hello everyone
today we are going to start a new season of GragTech New Horizons
unlike the previous season
we are not going to ditch the quest book
but we are going to follow it more strictly
the first thing we are asked to do
is to gather some dirt
which we can use to hide ourselves
if we can't get a bed in time for the first night
but that won't be an issue
since we managed to locate an abandoned building that we can shelter
and there we also found a bed
that will allow us to get some rest before moving on with the next task
getting some wood and some gravel
while wood is everywhere
finding gravel is a little bit trickier
the easiest way is probably to just look for a river
and check on its bed
one thing you'll probably notice
is that unlike vanilla Minecraft
you won't be getting any flint out of it
to obtain flint
you have to smash together three blocks of gravel
and that was also another quest
with that flint
we can now craft a rather expensive crafting table
and an axe and
flint is also going to be the material for our first tools
now that we have the basic equipment
we can start our journey of the self imposed challenge of completing every quest
to do that
we had to adventure across all sorts of biomes
we crossed dry biomes to find quick sands
we crossed a lake to find a magical forest
the only place where a rare blue tree grows
finally after crossing a Canyon
we managed to find a rare forest of bamboo for our last quest
once we get back home
we can brew a nice cup of tea before getting to the next chapter of quests
tier 0
this is the Stone Age level
so we have to start by doing some heavy work
and after gathering enough materials
we can craft enough bricks for a cook oven
we will momentorily build it under the floor
so that we can easily fuel the furnaces
that will polish the stone for our house
meanwhile we also built a small workshop
where we can craft better tools
it is composed of 3 tables
the first two will allow us to create patterns
and parts for the new tools
we can use all kind of easy to mold materials
the last table is the one
we used to assemble the parts into new tools
now that we have a pickaxe it is time to go mining
but we won't go in caves
or random holes like in normal Minecraft
in this modpack
ores spawn in a huge cluster located in a grid pattern
that means
we just have to dig at the center of the grid cells
to find clusters of minerals
and in this location we found oil sands
which we don't really need at the moment
so we move on to the next one
and after some digging we found limonite
an iron rich mineral
but it looks like our flint pickaxe can't break it
luckily
our quest book traded us an iron pickaxe head for some cobblestone
we can use a tool station to repair and upgrade our pickaxes with the newly acquired part
and with that we can finally collect iron
the other nice feature of our new pickaxes is that
the more we use it
the more it will level up
this will give modifier slots
which will allow us to add some enchanting materials to our tools
for example
we can add some lapis lazuli to our pickaxes to increase the amount of ore it harvests
one other useful modifier is Redstone
which will increase the working speed of our tools
next we built a smeltery
which is a variable size structure
which will allow us to melt metals
and cast parts for our tools
but tools made like that are just for the basic world interactions
to craft more advanced equipment
we need more refined tools
there are a lot of those
but we can start just with the basic ones
and with those
we can now work iron in all sorts of components
in case you are wondering what for
consider that doors are held together with screws
with all of those new parts
we can now craft many new things
we can start with a new lunch box
which will hold 6 different foods
helping us cycle our diet
we can upgrade our crafting table in a crafting station
which will access nearby chests and hold items when closed
we can also upgrade our chests using metals
increasing the storage capacity
and by using a lot of cotton and leather
we also managed to craft some backpacks
with all of that new equipment
,we can slowly work our way into harvesting a whole tree in the nearby forest
another great tool of this age is the ore finder wand
to use it
we insert a sample of something we want to find
and then we just keep walking around
until the wand starts to react
as you can see
you can even find diamonds just by searching for coal
and that's because there is always some coal around diamonds
the only thing left to do to complete this chapter is bronze
to do so we collect some copper and some tin
we grind those two materials into dust
and we mix everything up together
with that we have acquired bronze
and we can move on to the next chapter
steam age
as the name suggests
here we are going to work with some steam machinery
starting from a small bronze boiler
to get our first steam
we pipe that into a steam alloy smelter
which will allow us to do some more advanced metals
such as red alloy
and that material is part of the complicated piston recipe
with pistons we can finally get to the useful machinery
starting from a macerator
which main feature is doubling the amount of materials we get when working raw ores
since it doesn't get damage when used
it can also spare our mortars
finally
it can also recycle the stuff we find in dungeons
talking of which
there are a lot of things we can collect or find in the various structures laying around the world
and the best material you can find is steel
and by managing to collect 8 ingots
we can get some huge quality of life improvement
we use the first ingot to upgrade our pickaxes to steel
which can dig obsidian
we mix that with some steel and some aluminum
to obtain alumite
which we mold into larger plates
so that we can upgrade our tool station into Tool Forge
this upgrade will allow us to craft the most powerful and expensive tools
such as the lumber axe
which can chop down a whole tree in a single hit
or the hammer which is like 9 pickaxes
with all of that stuff
we can now build heavier machinery
such as the forge hammer
which will allow us to get cheaper metal plates
however that great improvement came with a huge cost
a lot of steam
now there are many more ways of producing steam
but all of them have some heating times
that won't play nicely with our consumption spikes
to fix those problems we made a huge buffer
a huge iron tank that can hold a lot of pressurized steam
and by also getting a new boiler
we can now power some bigger machines
we start with a steam grinder
which is like a macerator
but works 10 times faster while
being twice as power efficient
next we have the compressor multi block
finally and most importantly we have the steam presser
which does forge hammering
building the structure of those machines takes quite some materials
but we can reduce the cost
by having some of the parts being shared by different machines
however
running all of those at once is going to take a lot of steam
and the issue is not our steam production
but how quickly we can convey it to the steam machines
that means we need better pipes for our steam
for that upgrade
we can increase the size and use better materials
since we got in the basement
we also built a steam powered water pump
which will extract enough water to power the best steam generator in the game
the highest pressure solar boiler
now that energy is no longer an issue
we can start working on our next major project
a brick blast furnace
we start by shredding some bricks and some clay
we mix this so obtained dusts to obtain a refractory compound
fire clay
we press that material into bricks with our steam compressor
then we heat blast those bricks
and after mixing up some concrete
we have the building blocks for our upcoming blast furnace
the only issue left is to decide where to build it
and I mention that as an issue
because that machine is going to make pollution
I mean a single blast furnace isn't going to be much of a big deal
but we will want to build more than one
and we will want to cut on the building costs
and once we had multiple of those running for a couple of hours
we can start to see and feel the effects of pollution
anyways now that we have managed to obtain steel
there are many things we can do with it
but first things first
now that we have steel and flint
we can visit the Nether
this place is filled with nasty creatures
but it's the only place where we can find sulfur
which we need to process rubber
meanwhile
we can use some steel to make a couple of molds
like the plate one to work rubber into sheets
with those we can craft piston boots
which will make moving around way easier
and at the cost of a single steel ring
we can also get a better backpack
to carry around all of our tools
but the most useful thing we can craft with some more steel
is a charcoal piling lighter
to use it
we first have to dig a huge hole with some bricks on the bottom
we fill that hole with logs
and after covering all of the wood with dirt
we put our new machinery on top of it
this will start a long process
which will leave behind a lot of charcoal
that we can gather to fuel our blast furnaces
that will yield us a lot of steel
which we can use to craft some sturdy machine hulls
but those are just a supporting structure
to get any kind of task done
we are going to need at least some motor
and some kind of control circuitry
while motors are just a bunch of copper winding surrounding an iron core
circuits are more complicated
we start by laying some copper on a glued wooden board
next
we make some improvised resistors and some vacuum tubes out of whatever we have at our disposal
finally
we add some steel parts and some red alloy cables
to obtain some basic circuitry
with all of that stuff
we can build a steam turbine
which will turn steam into electricity
after connecting the steam fuel line and the output cables
we can start adding the most basic machines to our workshop
but after getting a wiremill to increase our wire production yield
and a centrifuge to extract glue and gold
we realized motors aren't enough for more intricate jobs
so we crafted a bunch more of components
that will unlock many more machines
but that's something we can see in the next episode
bye bye
大家好
今天我们要开始新一季的GTNH
不像上一季
我们不会放弃任务书的
而是更严格地遵循它
我们被要求做的第一件事
就是收集一些泥土
如果我们第一晚不能及时找到床
可以借助它挖三填一
但那不是问题
因为我们找到了可以藏身的废弃建筑
在那还找到了一张床
这可以使我们在进行下一任务前稍作歇息
也就是找些木头和燧石
木头无处不在
但寻找燧石有点棘手
最简单的方法可能就是找一条河
并检查河床
你可能会注意到一件事
不同于原版
你不会从沙砾获得燧石
要获取燧石
你得把三块沙砾砸在一起
这也是另一个任务
用那个燧石
我们现在可以制作一张相当昂贵的工作台
还有一把斧头
燧石也将是我们第一批工具的材料
现在我们有了基本设备
我们可以开始自我挑战的旅程，完成每一个任务
为此
我们不得不冒险穿越各种生物群落
我们穿越干燥的生物群落寻找流沙
我们穿过湖泊去寻找魔法森林
那是唯一生长稀有蓝树的地方
终于在穿过一个峡谷后
我们为最后一个任务找到了一片罕见竹林
一旦我们回到家
就可以在进入下一章任务之前泡杯好茶
也就是T0电压
这是石器时代的水平
所以我们必须从做一些繁重的工作开始
在收集到足够的材料后
我们可以为焦炉制作足够的砖块
我们会立刻把它建在地板下
这样用它给熔炉增添燃料会轻松不少
那熔炉将为我们的房子擦亮石头
同时我们还建了一个小车间
在那里我们可以制作更好的工具
它由3张桌子组成
前两个将允许我们制作模板
和新工具的零件
而我们可以使用各种易于成型的材料
这便是最后一张桌子的用途
我们用来把零件组装成新工具
现在我们有了镐，是时候去采矿了
但我们不会去找矿洞
或者像原版MC一样随地打孔
在这个整合包中
矿石以网格形式成堆生成
这意味着
我们只需要在区块中心挖掘
来寻找大矿脉
在这个地方我们发现了油砂
现在我们完全不需要它
所以我们继续找下一个
经过一番挖掘我们发现了褐铁矿
一种富含铁的矿物
但看起来我们的燧石镐挖不动
幸运地
我们的任务书用圆石给了个铁镐头
我们用工具站修理镐子
再用新获得的部件升级它
有了它，我们终于可以收集铁了
我们新镐的另一个优点是
我们用得越多
它就会升级得越多
这将提供强化插槽
这将使我们能够在工具中添加一些带有特殊效果的材料
例如
我们可以在镐中加入一些青金石来增加它收获的矿石量
另一个有用的材料是红石
这将提高我们工具的工作速度
接下来我们建了一个冶炼厂
这是一个可变大小的结构
这将使我们能够熔化金属
并为我们的工具铸造零件
但是像那样的工具只是用于基本的世界互动
要制造更先进的设备
我们需要一些更精细的工具
这类工具很多
但我们可以从最基本的开始
有了那些工具
我们现在可以用铁加工各种部件
如果你想知道它们的用途
想想门是用螺丝固定在一起的
有了所有这些新零件
我们现在可以制作许多新事物
我们可以从一个新的午餐盒开始
它将容纳6种不同的食物
帮助我们循环饮食
我们可以把工作台升级成合成站
它将连接到附近的箱子，并且能在关闭GUI时保留上面的物品
我们也可以用金属升级箱子
增加存储容量
通过使用大量的棉花和皮革
我们还制作了一些背包
有了所有的新设备
我们可以在附近的森林慢慢地砍下一整棵树
这个时代的另一个伟大工具是探矿魔杖
要使用它
我们放入想寻找的矿物原矿
然后我们就一直走来走去
直到魔杖开始反应
如你所见
你甚至可以通过煤炭来找到钻石
那是因为钻石周围总是有一些煤
这一章要做的只剩下青铜了
为此我们收集了一些铜和锡
把它们磨成粉末
再把其混合在一起
这样我们就获得了青铜
我们可以继续下一章
蒸汽时代
顾名思义
在这里，我们将使用一些蒸汽机械
从一个小青铜锅炉开始
得到我们的第一升蒸汽
我们把它输送到蒸汽合金冶炼炉
这将使我们能够制造一些更高级的金属
比如红色合金
这种材料是复杂活塞配方的一部分
有了活塞，我们终于可以做一些好机器了
从粉碎机开始
它可以使我们处理原矿获得二倍增产
因为使用时不会损坏
也能省下我们的研钵
最后
它还可以回收我们在地牢里找到的东西
说到地牢
我们可以在分布在世界各地的各种结构中获得大量材料
能找到的最好材料是钢
我们设法收集了8个
将为我们的游戏体验上个档次
我们用第一个锭将镐升级为钢
它可以挖黑曜石
我们把它和一些钢和铝混合
获取锌曜钢/耐酸铝
我们把它塑造成大板
这样我们就可以将工具站升级为工具装配台
这次升级将使我们能够制作最强大、最昂贵的工具
比如伐木斧
一击就能砍倒一整棵树
或者是九镐合一的锤子
有了所有这些东西
我们现在可以建造更“重”的机器
比如锻造锤
这将使我们能够减本增产板子
然而，巨大的进步伴随着巨大的成本
也就是大量蒸汽
现在有更多产生蒸汽的方法
但是它们都有一些暖机时间
它们对耗能高峰有些乏力
为了解决这些问题，我们做了一个巨大的缓冲
一个可以容纳大量蒸汽的巨大铁罐
并且借助于新的锅炉
我们现在可以驱动一些更大的机器
我们从蒸汽研磨机开始
这就像粉碎机一样
但工作速度快10倍
两倍的能效
接下来是多方块压缩机
最后也是最重要的是蒸汽锻造锤
进行狠狠地砸击❤️
这些机器的结构方块需要相当多的材料
但我们可以通过共享一些结构方块降低成本
然而
同时运行它们会需要很多蒸汽
问题不在于我们的蒸汽生产
而是输送到机器的速率
这意味着我们需要更好的蒸汽管道
对于那个升级
我们可以增加尺寸并使用更好的材料
既然我们进了地下室
我们还建造了一个蒸汽驱动的水泵
它将提取足够的水来驱动游戏中最好的蒸汽发生器
†高级太阳能锅炉†
既然能源不再是问题
我们可以开始下一个大项目了
砖高炉
我们先粉碎一些砖块和粘土
我们混合这种得到的粉尘得到一种耐火化合物
耐火粘土
我们用蒸汽压缩机将材料压成砖
然后我们对那些砖块进行熔炼
在混合了一些混凝土之后
我们为即将到来的高炉准备好了结构方块
剩下的唯一问题是决定在哪里建造它
我把这认为是一个问题
是因为那台机器会制造污染
我是说一个高炉没什么大不了的
但我们想要建造不止一个
我们会想削减建筑成本
一旦它们开始运行了几个小时
我们就可以开始感受到，甚至看到污染的后果
不管怎样，现在我们已经设法获得了钢铁
我们可以用它做很多事情
但首先
既然我们有了打火石
我们可以去下界了
这地方到处都是肮脏的生物
但这是唯一能找到硫磺的地方
我们用它来加工出橡胶
同时
我们可以用一些钢做几个模具
就像盘子一样，将橡胶加工成片材
有了这些，我们可以制作活塞靴
这将使四处走动更容易
以一个钢圈为代价
我们也可以得到一个更好的背包
用来随身携带所有的工具
但我们能用钢铁制造的最有用的东西
是木炭堆点火器
要使用它
我们首先要挖一个大洞
底部放一些砖块
我们用木头填满它
用泥土覆盖所有的木头后
我们把新机器放在上面
这将开始一个漫长的过程
结束后产出大量木炭
我们将其收集好为高炉增添燃料
那样我们就能获得很多钢
我们可以用它来制作一些坚固机器外壳
但这些只是支撑结构
要完成各种类型的任务
我们至少需要一些马达
和某种控制电路
而马达只是一堆围绕铁芯的铜绕组
电路比较复杂
我们先在粘好的木板上放些铜
然后
我们利用手头现有的材料制作了一些简易电阻和真空管
最后
我们加上一些钢外壳和一些红色合金电缆
获得一些基本电路
有了所有这些东西
我们可以造一个蒸汽轮机
这将把蒸汽转化为电能
连接蒸汽管道和输出电缆后
我们可以开始为车间添加LV机器
但是在得到一个线缆轧机来提高线材产量后
以及一个离心机用来提取胶水和金
我们意识到马达不足以完成更复杂的工作
所以我们制作了更多的组件
这将解锁更多的机器
但这就将是下期的内容了
拜拜
（3*3区块对应一个格雷矿脉）